baekdal.com 2019-07-19

# Privacy Policy - Baekdal Plus

Hi there,

On this page you will be able to find complete details about how Baekdal.com uses data and what is collected about you. You will also be able to delete your data if you so choose.

Baekdal.com works on the principle that **you are the only one who can decide what you want to share**. As such, Baekdal.com only collects and uses data that you have chosen to provide.

So what data is collected and used by Baekdal.com? 

_Please note: Because you have not logged in, you are currently identified as a ‘free user’. If you have an account and want more detailed data, **please log in first**. _

* * *

## Your data explained: First-time / free users:

As a first-time/free user, Baekdal.com collects **zero personally identifiable data about you**. This includes our analytics, where we only store non-personal data.

For instance, we do track what articles you look at, and even if you read them. But, in the database, there is no field that stores any form of user ID that could be used to track you specifically.

In simple terms, there is no way for baekdal.com to know that you are the one reading a specific article. We only know that someone did.

So, as a free user, **baekdal.com stores zero data about you**.

### List of your data

Because you are not logged in, we are identifying you as a ‘free user’. As such we have **no personally identifying data** stored about you.

As in **none!**

* * *

## 3rd party data and exceptions

There are five different exceptions to the above:

### Newsletter

The Baekdal Plus newsletter is free for anyone and is managed separately from Baekdal Plus subscriptions.

You can always unsubscribe from it using the link at the bottom of each email, and, as soon as you do this, your email is permanently deleted from the mailing list. 

You can also contact [plus@baekdal.com](mailto:plus@baekdal.com) and tell us to delete it for you. In any case, the email address used to sign-up for the Baekdal Plus newsletter is only stored as long as you are an active subscriber.

### Embedded videos

In several of the articles here on Baekdal.com, there is a link to an embedded video from, for instance, YouTube. By default, these videos are not loaded automatically, so unless you specifically click on them, **nothing is sent to YouTube’s servers**. 

In other words, it is entirely up to you if you want YouTube to play the video, because you are specifically asked if you want to do this each time. Keep in mind that, if you play a video, YouTube might collect data about you, and they might show you an ad on top of the video. 

### Google analytics

Baekdal.com also uses Google Analytics, but not in the way you are used to. First of all, we are **not sending any personally identifiable data to Google** , neither a user ID or even your IP address. The only data we send is non-personally identifiable data.

We are not even loading Google Analytics into your browser, so there is no way that Google can track you because of what you do here on baekdal.com.

### Cookies

Baekdal.com does use a cookie, but in a very limited way. Only **a single cookie is set** , and the value of it depends on what type of user you are. If you are a free user, the cookie is set with a "baekdal=free" value, which **does not include any personally identifying information**. 

This cookie is only used as a way to manage the site. It does not track you, or identify you in any way.

However, if you create an account (free trial or Baekdal Plus), the cookie will be set with an ID. This is used to automatically log you in, so that you don’t have to do this every time you want to look at an article (which would be annoying).

Baekdal.com is also using [Cloudflare](https://www.cloudflare.com/) to protect the server from attacks, and, as part of this, Cloudflare is also setting a cookie called "__cfduid". This cookie exist solely for technical reasons. It does not correspond to any user ID, and **does not store any personally identifiable information**.

### Log files

Finally, Baekdal.com does keep a log file with all the raw requests being sent to this site. This file includes:

  * The pages people requested
  * People’s IP addresses
  * What browser you use (the ‘USER-AGENT’ as it is called technically).

This file is **automatically deleted after four weeks** , and it’s used **solely to protect against security threats**. For instance, if someone tried to hack the server, this file is what is used to figure out what is going on.

Similarly, Baekdal.com is managing the network through a company called Cloudflare, and here the same thing applies. While your IP address is sent through them, it’s not collected or used to track you in any way. Cloudflare automatically deletes this data after 3 days. 

_Legal note: Under GDPR, security related data is an exception in accordance to Article 6, Paragraph 1, Point F: Processing shall be lawful only if and to the extent that at least one of the following applies: […] (f) processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the controller - Recital 49: The processing of personal data to the extent strictly necessary and proportionate for the purposes of ensuring network and information security [...]._

* * *

## Contact Baekdal.com - Privacy Information

  * By email: [plus@baekdal.com](mailto:plus@baekdal.com)
  * By mail: Baekdal.com, Odinsgade 51, 7100 Vejle, Denmark
